<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Patel Geography Trivia</string>
    <string name="states">Pennsylvania</string>
    <string name="cities">Pittsburgh</string>
    <string name="text">

        There are 195 countries in the world today. \n\n This total comprises 193 countries
        that are member states of the United Nations and 2 countries that are non-member observer states:
        \nthe Holy See and the State of Palestine.
        \n\nNot in the list\n\n
        Not included in this total count of 195 countries are:\n

        Taiwan - the United Nations considers it represented by the People\'s Republic of China \n
        The Cook Islands and Niue, both states in free association with New Zealand which are members of several UN specialized agencies and have been recognized "full treaty-making capacity", but are neither member states nor non-member observer states.
        \nDependencies (or dependent territories, dependent areas, dependencies) and Areas of Special Sovereignty (autonomous territories)
        \nOther countries recognized by the United Nations as not being self-governing
        \n\n
        Where are they located? \n \n
        54 countries are in Africa
        \n48 in Asia
        \n44 in Europe
        \n33 in Latin America and the Caribbean
        \n14 in Oceania
        \n2 in Northern America</string>

    <string name="state1">The United States of America is a federal republic consisting of 50 states
        (four of which use the term commonwealth rather than state in their full, legal state name),
        a federal district (where the nation\'s seat of government—Washington, D.C), five major territories,
        and various possessions.\nThe 48 contiguous states and Washington, D.C., are in central
        North America between Canada and Mexico. The state of Alaska is in the northwestern part of North America
        (also bordering Canada) and the state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific.\n</string>
    <string name="question">What is the nickname for the state of Pennsylvania?</string>
    <string name="ci">Correct or \nIncorrect</string>
    <string name="t">TRIES: \n</string>


</resources>
